Guide to the Maurice Hindus papers M2002
Special Collections and University Archives, Colgate University Libraries
- Personal correspondence, 1924-1969
  - ALS, Paolo Vivante to Hindus, Austin, regarding personal/visa difficulties, 1964 November 25 (Box 2, Folder 89)
  - TLS, John Vore (?) to Hindus, London, regarding article, 1929 May 22 (Box 2, Folder 90)
  - TLS, John Vore (?) to Hindus, London, regarding chapters, 1929 June 28 (Box 2, Folder 91)
  - ALS, Hugh Walpole, Piccadilly, regarding personal, 1925 November 14 (Box 2, Folder 92)
  - TC, Hugh Walpole to Hindus, regarding personal, 1929 November 14 (Box 2, Folder 93)
  - TLS, Meyer W. Weisgal, Israel, regarding reaction to article, 1949 August 2 (Box 2, Folder 94)
  - ALS, Helen Kahle Wickes, California, regarding Christmas, 1969 December 19 (Box 2, Folder 95)
  - TC, Hindus to Willkie (Wendell J.), New York City, regarding personal, 1943 July 9 (Box 2, Folder 96)
  - TCS, Hindus to Willkie (Wendell J.), New York City, regarding personal, 1943 June 26 (Box 2, Folder 97)
  - TL, Hindus to Wendell Willkie, New York City, regarding Fin President, 1940 August 8 (Box 2, Folder 98)
  - TLS, Wendell Willkie to Hindus, Colorado Springs, regarding letter of Aug. 8, 1940 August 10 (Box 2, Folder 99)
  - TL, Yugoslav Information Center to Hindus, New York, New York, regarding newsletter, 1967 April (Box 2, Folder 100)
  - TL, To Hindus, regarding Where are you?, 1927 December 7 (Box 2, Folder 101)
  - ALS, To Hindus, Berlin, regarding personal, 1938 July 19 (Box 2, Folder 102)
  - TLS, To Hindus, Waterloo Place, S.W.I., regarding personal, 1938 June 16 (Box 2, Folder 103)
- Correspondence with Frances McClernan, 1939-1961
  - 14 TLS, Hindus to Frances McClernan, various, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - 7 TLS, Hindus to Frances McClernan, various, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - 5 TLS, Hindus to Frances McClernan, various, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Telegram, Hindus to Frances McClernan, Moscow, 1958 July 18 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Telegram, Hindus to Frances McClernan, Hampton, Virginia, 1958 March 12 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - 18 TLS, Hindus to Frances McClernan, various, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - TLS, Hindus to Frances McClernan, various, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - 14 TLS, Hindus to Frances McClernan, various, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Telegram, Hindus to Frances McClernan, Belgrade, 1955 June 17 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - 15 TLS, Hindus to Frances McClernan, various, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - 6 TLS, Hindus to Frances McClernan, various, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - 2 TLS, Hindus to Frances McClernan, various, 1951? (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - 14 TLS, Hindus to Frances McClernan, various, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - 3 TLS, Hindus to Frances McClernan, various, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - 2 TLS, Hindus to Frances McClernan, various, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Review of "The Black Book" compiled by Frances McClernan, et al., 1946 June 13 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Invitation to Reception at the Consulate General of USSR, Miss Frances McClernan, no year February 10 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Ticket for Miss Frances McClernan, undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Telegram, Hindus to Frances McClernan, Warszawa, 1939 August 26 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - TLS, Hindus to Frances, Washington, D.C., 1942 May 29 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Telegram, Hindus to Frances McClernan, Kouibychev, 1942 June 15 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Telegram, Hindus to Frances McClernan, Praha, 1945 November 14 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Telegram, Hindus to Frances McClernan, Praha, 1945 December 2 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Telegram, Hindus to Frances McClernan, Praha, 1947 June 16 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Telegram, Hindus to Frances McClernan, Anna Maria, Florida, 1947 December 23 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Telegram, Hindus to Frances McClernan, Detroit, Michigan, 1951 February 7 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Book reviews and correspondence, 1926-1968
  - Broken Earth, 1926-1954
    - TL, Hindus to Trachtenberg, City Club of New York, regarding Broken Earth, 1929 November 23 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - TL, Hindus to Trachtenberg, Rochester, New York, regarding Broken Earth, 1929 December 10 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - TL, Hindus to Trachtenberg, New York City, regarding Legal suit--Broken Earth, 1929 December 28 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - TL, Hindus to Mr. Van Doren, New York City, regarding Broken Earth, 1929 December 26 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - ALS, Lilu Iniossn (?) to Hindus, Isafiordar (?), Iceland, regarding Broken Earth, 1928 May 7 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - ALS, Gantt (?) to Hindus, Lenningrad, regarding Book-Broken Earth, 1926 September 13 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - TLS, Emanuel E. Harper to Hindus, New York, New York, regarding copyright Broken Earth, 1954 January 6 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - New York Times, review of Broken Earth, 1926 July 25 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Pontoon Z. Doakes,Rocky Mt. News, review of Broken Earth, 1931 November 22 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - St. Paul News, review of Broken Earth, 1931 November 22 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - New York Daily Mirror, review of Broken Earth, 1931 November 28 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Philadelphia Inquirer, review of Broken Earth, 1931 November 28 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - New Leader, Virginia, review of Broken Earth, 1931 November 30 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Alan Nash, Buffalo, New York, review of Broken Earth, 1931 December 6 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Lewis B. Lesley, California, review of Broken Earth, 1931 December 6 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - John George Harris, Virginia, review of Broken Earth, 1931 December 6 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Milwaukee Journal, review of Broken Earth, 1931 December 12 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Raleigh News Observer, review of Broken Earth, 1931 December 13 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - D.R.W., Cincinnati, review of Broken Earth, 1931 December 15 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Christian Science Monitor, Boston, review of Broken Earth, 1931 December 19 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - I.A. Levitan,Evanston News Index, review of Broken Earth, 1931 December 23 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - The New Republic, review of Broken Earth, 1931 December 23 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Guy V. Miller, Pennsylvania, review of Broken Earth, 1931 December 31 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - ?, review of Broken Earth, 1932 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Yale News, review of Broken Earth, 1932 January (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - New Haven Journal, review of Broken Earth, 1932 January 2 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Globe Democrat, Missouri, review of Broken Earth, 1932 January 9 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Bradford Young,The Church Man, review of Broken Earth, 1932 January 9 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Indianapolis News, review of Broken Earth, 1932 January 16 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Jacob Trapp, Salt Lake City, review of Broken Earth, 1932 January 17 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - H.R. Foster, Minneapolis, review of Broken Earth, 1932 January 17 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Denver Post, review of Broken Earth, 1932 January 17 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Plain Dealer, Cleveland, Ohio, review of Broken Earth, 1932 January 24 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - The Christian Century, review of Broken Earth, 1932 January 27 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Ben Ray Redman, New York City, review of Broken Earth, 1932 February 7 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Observer, North Carolina, review of Broken Earth, 1932 February 14 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - The Congregationalist, review of Broken Earth, 1932 March 17 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Red Bread, 1931-1968
    - TLS, Susan Matthewman to Jonathon Cope, Harvard University; TLS Hindus to Susan Matthewman, New York, New York; TL, Donald W. Oliver to Hindus, Harvard University, regarding Red Bread, 1966 October 31, 1966 December 12, 1968 July 2 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Michigan Law Review, review of Red Bread, 1931-1932 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Malcolm W. Davis,Yale Review, review of Red Bread, 1931 Autumn (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Clinton Rogers Woodruff,The Living Church, review of Red Bread, 1931 November 14 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Charlotte Reeve Conover, Ohio, review of Red Bread, 1931 November 30 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Vsevolod Fedoroff, review of Red Bread, 1931 December (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - Harry Hansen Chicago Daily News; Will Durant New York Herald Tribune; review of Red Bread, 1931 December 20 (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Chicago Tribune, review of Red Bread, 1932 January 6 (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - Mrs. T.G. Burns, Rockwell City, review of Red Bread, 1932 February 28 (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - Minneapolis Star, review of Red Bread, no year May 16 (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - A.W.M.,The Standard, review of Red Bread, 1932 March (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - TLS, Marjorie Currey to Hindus, New York, New York, regarding copyright Broken Earth and Red Bread, 1958 May 26 (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - Hound and Horn, review of Humanity Uprooted,Red Bread, 1930, 1931 (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - The Bookman's Monthly Score, review of Red Bread,Humanity Uprooted, 1931, 1930 December (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - American Library Bulletin, review of Broken Earth,Humanity Uprooted,Red Bread, 1930, 1931 (Box 4, Folder 52)
    - Courier Journal, review of Humanity Uprooted,Red Bread, 1932 April 3 (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - Herald, review of Humanity Uprooted,Red Bread, 1931 December 26 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - In Search of a Future, 1949-1952
    - Justice William O. Douglas to Hindus, Washington, D.C., regarding In Search of a Future, 1952 February 11 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - TLS, D.J. Bleifuss to Hindus, San Francisco, regarding In Search of a Future, 1949 July 21 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Fitzhugh Turner,New York Herald Tribune, review of In Search of a Future, 1949 February 27 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Hitler Cannot Conquer Russia, 1941
    - Lewis Gannett,New York Herald Tribune, review of Hitler Cannot Conquer Russia, 1941 September 26 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Joseph B. Phillips,New York Herald Tribune, review of Hitler Cannot Conquer Russia, 1941 September 28 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - William L. Shirer,The Saturday Review, review of Hitler Cannot Conquer Russia, 1941 October 4 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Alicia Patterson,Sunday News, review of Hitler Cannot Conquer Russia, 1941 October 5 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Carl Sandburg, Boston, review of Hitler Cannot Conquer Russia, 1941 October 19 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Mother Russia, 1943
    - Benjamin DeCasseres, review of Mother Russia, 1943 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Orville Prescott,New York Times, review of Mother Russia, 1943 June 4 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - The Kremlin's Human Dilemma, 1966-1967
    - TLS, Oscar and Becky to Hindus, regarding The Kremlin's Human Dilemma, 1967 March 15 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Sylvia Rothchild,The Jewish Advocate, review of The Kremlin's Human Dilemma, 1967 June 22 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - TL, Hindus to Cyrus Brooks, regarding The Kremlin's Human Dilemma, 1966 August 15 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - TL, Hindus to Cyrus Brooks, regarding The Kremlin's Human Dilemma, 1966 August 15 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - TLS, Y. Katahira to Hindus, Tokyo, Japan; TL, Hindus to Y. Katahira, New York, New York, regarding The Kremlin's Human Dilemma, 1967 February 13, 1967 February 25 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - 2 TC, F.A. Brockhaus to Hindus, Wiesbaden, Germany, regarding The Kremlin's Human Dilemma, 1966 December 12 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - TL, Hindus to F.A. Brockhaus, regarding The Kremlin's Human Dilemma, 1966 August 15 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - TLS, F.A. Brockhaus to Hindus, Germany, regarding The Kremlin's Human Dilemma, 1966 November 3 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - TLS, Lawrence Freundlich to Hindus, New York, New York, regarding The Kremlin's Human Dilemma, 1967 January 6 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - TL, Hindus to Mr. Freundlich, New York, New York, regarding The Kremlin's Human Dilemma, 1967 February 18 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - TL, Hindus to Mr. Freundlich, regarding The Kremlin's Human Dilemma, 1967 January 5 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Russia and Japan, 1942
    - TLS, Hindus to Mr. Iams, New York City, regarding Russia and Japan, 1942 April 8 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Time, review of Russia and Japan, 1942 June 8 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Sidney Justin Harris, review of Russia and Japan, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Promotional Review, review of Russia and Japan, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - House Without a Roof, 1961-1962
    - TLS, Arnold Smith to Hindus, Moscow, regarding House Without a Roof, 1962 September 24 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - TLS, Hester Green to Hindus, London, regarding House Without a Roof, 1962 November 29 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - TLS, Hester Green to Hindus, London, regarding House Without a Roof, 1962 March 9 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Martha McGregor,New York Post, review of House Without a Roof, 1961 August 20 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Promotional Review, review of House Without a Roof, undated (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Harrison E. Salisburg,New York Times, review of House Without a Home, 1961 August 20 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Merle Fainsod,Herald Tribune, review of House Without a Roof, 1961 August 20 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Ethel and Stephen P. Dunn, Columbia University Forum, regarding House Without a Roof, 1962 Spring (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - To Sing with the Angels, 1941-1942
    - John Cournos,New York Times, review of To Sing with the Angels, 1941 January 26 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - TLS, Angelina Tauchen to Hindus, Omaha, Nebraska, regarding To Sing with the Angels, 1941 September 1 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - TLS, Rev. George P. Eastman to Doubleday, Doran and Company, Summit, New Jersey, regarding To Sing with the Angels, 1941 October 12 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - TLS, Bertram T. Rumhle to Hindus, London, regarding Proceeds from Russia Fights On and To Sing with the Angels, 1942 May 22 (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Arthur J. Sheehan, review of To Sing with the Angels, no year February 15 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Crisis in Kremlin, 1953-1954
    - Merle Fainsod,Herald Tribune, review of Crisis in the Kremlin, 1953 December 6 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - TLS, Gretchen Eisner to Hindus, New York, New York, regarding royalties-Magda and Crisis in Kremlin, 1954 August 19 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - TLS, to Hindus, Beograd, regarding Crisis in Kremlin, 1954 February 15 (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - TLS, W. Averell Harriman to Hindus, New York, regarding Crisis in Kremlin, 1953 December 10 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - TLS, John J. McCloy to Hindus, New York City, New York, regarding Crisis in Kremlin, 1953 November 30 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Other works, 1937-1967
    - TLS, Stewart Richardson to Hindus, New York, New York, regarding Svetlana, 1967 August 8 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Basil Woon,San Francisco News, review of Magda, no year February 2 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - TL, Hindus to Stapf, regarding Gallery, 1966 October 25 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - TLS, Marjorie Currey to Hindus, New York, New York, regarding rights to Great Offensive, 1960 August 17 (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - TLS, Harrison Smith to Hindus, New York, New York, regarding Russian Twilight, 1937 October 1 (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - TLS, Louis Johnson to Hindus, Washington, D.C., regarding Kremlin's Major Blunders, 1953 September 1 (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - TLS, Victor Gollancz, Ltd. to Hindus, London, regarding manuscript, 1949 January 18 (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - TLS, Justice William O. Douglas to Hindus, Washington, D.C. regarding book on Russia, 1943 June 12 (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - TLS, Hindus to Mr. E. Cohen, regarding review, 1950 May 14 (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - TLS, M. Kerner to Hindus, Boston, regarding Bright Passage, 1949 December 30 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Humanity Uprooted, 1928-1965
    - TLS, Robert K. Haas to Hindus, New York, New York, regarding rights to Humanity Uprooted, 1945 June 18 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Ernestine Evans, New York City, review of Humanity Uprooted, 1929 October 20 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - New York Herald Tribune, review of Humanity Uprooted, 1929 October 22 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - E.H.G., London, review of Humanity Uprooted, 1929 October 26 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Herald Tribune, review of Humanity Uprooted, 1929 November 5 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Paul Hutchinson,Christian Century, review of Humanity Uprooted, 1929 November 6 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Edward T. Devine,Outlook, review of Humanity Uprooted, 1929 November 20 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - American Mercury, review of Humanity Uprooted, 1929 December (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - The Living Age Advertiser, review of Humanity Uprooted, 1929 December (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Tulane Law Review, review of Humanity Uprooted, 1929 December (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - TLS, Paul Ferster to Hindus, Cleveland, Ohio, regarding request to reprint Humanity Uprooted, 1965 February 27 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - TLS, F.E. Hill to Hindus, New York, New York, regarding Humanity Uprooted, 1928 April 30 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - TLS, Robert P. Drake to Jonathan Cape, Chicago; Excerpt from Dr. Copelond Smith's broadcast, regarding Humanity Uprooted, 1931 March 4-March 5 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - TL, Fannie Hurst to Hindus, regarding Humanity Uprooted, 1929 December 12 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - TLS, Lawrence F. Abbott to Jonathan Cape and Harrison Smith, New York, New York, regarding Humanity Uprooted, 1930 October 16 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - TLS, Nicholas Klein to Jonathan Cape and Harrison Smith, Cincinnati, regarding Humanity Uprooted, 1930 October 2 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Martine Golde, New York City, review of Humanity Uprooted, 1929 December 6 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - R.M. Fox,Irish Statesman, review of Humanity Uprooted, 1929 December 7 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Light, review of Humanity Uprooted, 1929 December 9 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - The Times, review of Humanity Uprooted, 1929 December 26 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Observer, review of Humanity Uprooted, 1929 December 29 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Foreign Affairs, review of Humanity Uprooted, 1930 January (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - H.C. Engelbreacht, New York City, review of Humanity Uprooted, 1930 January (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Mark Van Doren,Theatre Guild Magazine, review of Humanity Uprooted, 1930 January (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - The Christian Advocate, review of Humanity Uprooted, 1930 January 9 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Phillip H. Jewett, Philadelphia, review of Humanity Uprooted, 1930 January 11 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Harry Emerson Wildes, Philadelphia, review of Humanity Uprooted, 1930 January 18 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - A.K.,Jewish Journal, review of Humanity Uprooted, 1930 February 5 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Joshua Kunitz,The Nation, review of Humanity Uprooted, 1930 February 5 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - P.M.I., Montreal, review of Humanity Uprooted, 1930 February 22 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Harry Fosdick and Reinhold Neibuhr, review of Humanity Uprooted, 1930 February-March (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Book League Monthly, review of Humanity Uprooted, 1930 April (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - R.E. Wolseley, Illinois, review of Humanity Uprooted, 1930 April 12 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - M.V.R.,The West Virginian, review of Humanity Uprooted, 1930 April 14 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Saturday Review, review of Humanity Uprooted, 1930 April 26 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Margaret Isabel Lawrence, Toronto, review of Humanity Uprooted, 1930 June 7 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Edgar Snow, Shanghai, review of Humanity, 1930 June 7 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Sherman Daily Democrat, Texas, review of Humanity Uprooted, 1930 June 29 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Hugh S. Tigner,Christian Leader, review of Humanity Uprooted, 1930 July 12 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - Information Service, review of Humanity Uprooted, 1930 July 19 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Herald Tribune, review of Humanity Uprooted;Herald Tribune, review of Humanity Uprooted, 1930 July 20, 1930 July 27 (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - John Wanhope, Albany, review of Humanity Uprooted, 1930 July 20 (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - Detroit News, review of Humanity Uprooted, 1930 August 3 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Stella G. Stefton, Cedar Rapids, review of Humanity Uprooted, 1930 August 10 (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - Detroit Free Press, review of Humanity Uprooted;Detriot Free Press, review of Humanity Uprooted, 1930 August 10, 1930 August 17 (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - Leonard Hodgson,Living Church, review of Humanity Uprooted, 1930 August 23 (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - Outlook, review of Humanity Uprooted, 1930 August 27 (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - J.L.F.America, review of Humanity Uprooted, 1930 August 30 (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - Annie Kate Gilbert,Woman's Press, review of Humanity Uprooted, 1930 September (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - B.D.,Scribners, review of Humanity Uprooted, 1930 September (Box 6, Folder 50)
    - Hunter Bulletin, review of Humanity Uprooted, 1930 October 14 (Box 6, Folder 51)
    - E.B. Shultz, review of Humanity Uprooted, 1930 November (Box 6, Folder 52)
    - Walter E. Myer,Civil Education, review of Humanity Uprooted, 1930 November 14 (Box 6, Folder 53)
    - Travel, review of Humanity Uprooted, 1930 December (Box 6, Folder 54)
    - William Lyon Phelps, review of Humanity Uprooted, 1930 December (Box 6, Folder 55)
    - R.L.,Jewish Layman, review of Humanity Uprooted, 1931 January (Box 6, Folder 56)
    - Travel, review of Humanity Uprooted, 1931 February (Box 6, Folder 57)
    - Monte Cooper,Commercial Appeal, review of Humanity Uprooted, 1931 February 15 (Box 6, Folder 58)
    - Walter H. ?,Joliet Independent, review of Humanity Uprooted, 1931 February 19 (Box 6, Folder 59)
    - W.H.M.,Joliet Universalist, review of Humanity Uprooted, 1931 February 20 (Box 6, Folder 60)
    - Catholic Sun, review of Humanity Uprooted, 1931 May 21 (Box 6, Folder 61)
    - Franklin D. Elmer, Jr.,The Baptist, review of Humanity Uprooted, 1931 September 19 (Box 6, Folder 62)
    - G.J.,Reformed Church Messenger, review of Humanity Uprooted, 1931 November 26 (Box 6, Folder 63)
    - Banner Herald, review of Humanity Uprooted, 1931 December 27 (Box 6, Folder 64)
    - Mary Burke King, California, review of Humanity Uprooted, 1932 February 7 (Box 6, Folder 65)
    - The Chinese Recorder, review of Humanity Uprooted, [1929 or 1931] October (Box 6, Folder 66)
    - Christian Advocate, review of Humanity Uprooted, [1929 or 1931] November (Box 6, Folder 67)
    - Boston Evening Transcript, review of Humanity Uprooted, [1929 or 1931] December 11 (Box 6, Folder 68)
    - Book-of-the-Month, review of Humanity Uprooted, [1929 or 1931] (Box 6, Folder 69)
    - A.A.Y.,Plain Dealer, review of Humanity Uprooted, [1929 or 1931] (Box 6, Folder 70)
    - Missionary Review of the World, review of Humanity Uprooted, [1929 or 1932] (Box 6, Folder 71)
    - El Libro, review of Humanity Uprooted, circa 1930 (Box 6, Folder 72)
    - Pacific Affairs, review of Humanity Uprooted, circa 1931 (Box 6, Folder 73)
    - Montreal Guardian, review of Humanity Uprooted, [1930 or 1931] January 17 (Box 6, Folder 74)
    - Keeping Mentally Fit, review of Humanity Uprooted, [1930 or 1931] May 4 (Box 6, Folder 75)
    - Bookman, review of Humanity Uprooted, [1930 or 1931] May (Box 6, Folder 76)
    - R.A. Lapsley,The Presbyterian Survey, review of Humanity Uprooted, [1930 or 1931] June (Box 6, Folder 77)
    - The Virginia Quarterly Review, review of Humanity Uprooted, [1930 or 1931] July (Box 6, Folder 78)
    - Eleanor Hubbard Garst,Better Homes and Gardens, review of Humanity Uprooted, [1930 or 1931] July (Box 6, Folder 79)
    - Christian Herald, review of Humanity Uprooted, [1930 or 1931] July (Box 6, Folder 80)
    - American Historical Review, review of Humanity Uprooted, [1930 or 1932] January (Box 6, Folder 81)
    - H. Allen Smith, New York, review of Humanity Uprooted, [1930 or 1932] January 20 (Box 6, Folder 82)
  - Moscow Skies, 1936-1937
    - Alfred Kazin,New York Times, review of Moscow Skies, 1936 September 27 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - J.A.H.,British Weekly, review of Under Moscow Skies, 1936 September 24 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Lewis Gannett, review of Moscow Skies, undated (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - M.M.C.,The Forum, review of Moscow Skies, 1936 October (Box 7, Folder 17)